moviebeat.in 2012-09-23

# MovieBeat

**MovieBeat Privacy Policy**  

Welcome,  
MovieBeat Privacy Policy is designed to provide clarity about the information we collect and how we use it to provide a better social gaming experience. By accepting MovieBeat (A Cloudion Labs Product) Privacy Policy and Terms of Service during registration or game installation, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

MovieBeat is committed to your privacy and makes every effort to ensure the confidentiality of your personal information. We respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted a corporate wide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide.

**Information We Collect**

User - Provided Information: When you add a MovieBeat application in your social networking site or in a mobile device, you provide us with the information associated with our account on the site in accordance with the site's Terms of Service. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your e mail messages, your email address and our responses. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service. You may provide us information in User Content you post to the Service. You may provide payment information to our payment partner if you conduct paid transactions on the Service; such information is subject to the payment provider's privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy.

Cookies: We use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data. When you visit us, we may send one or more cookies (a small file with a series of characters) to your computer; with the help of these cookies your browser can be recognized. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our services, among other things to store your user preferences, to improve search results and relevance of advertisements and to update user trends. We may also use cookies in advertising services to help advertisers and publishers present and control advertisements on the Website. We may place cookies in your browser when you visit a website or click on the advertisement. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, however, you could re-set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie has been sent. In some cases that may impact your ability to use MovieBeat.

Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any web page. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

Clear Gifs Information: When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML based e-mails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make MovieBeat better for our users.

**How We Use Your Information**

For a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience, we collect, store and use your information. By providing MovieBeat your email address, including by adding MovieBeat application on your social network, you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. You also agree that we may send you notifications of activity on the Service to the email address you give us, in accordance with any applicable privacy settings. We even use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you want to opt out from the above mentioned process, Opt out option is also provided, thus it will prevent you from receiving further e mails regarding updates, product improvement etc.

The information may be used:

*To process your payment for game membership subscriptions.

*To provide our customer support service, and to verify any claims or requests you make if you use our customer support service.

*To send service announcements which contain important information about our service, our site, or your account. (For example an email reminder is sent to members if a subscription payment is due).

*To aggregate information to generate anonymous statistics regarding use of our services. We may share this anonymous information with our partners, affiliates and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

*We also use your personal information for our own internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs.

*To disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or to enforce legal rights.

*Any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. We may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business, affiliate partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of our users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.

*Free Gifts, Discounts, Special Contests, Special Offers or Promotions. We may occasionally present a free gifts, discounts, special contests, special offers or promotion that is sponsored by us or another company. To qualify for entry in those free gifts, special offers, discounts, contests or promotions, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s)or with others, we will provide a statement to that effect in the options with terms.

*IP Address. All communication on the internet takes place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address that any connection is made from. We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly. We respect your privacy, except as specified above we will not sell, rent, or disclose your personal information to other companies. We will not use your email address to send you 'spam'.

**How We Share Your Information**

Personally Identifiable Information: MovieBeat may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of MovieBeat (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

MovieBeat may disclose information about you to select business partners in order to provide you with advertising and promotional information and opportunities that we think may be of interest to you. We do not give our partners an independent right to share this information.

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings. You may change your privacy settings on the Service with the features provided by the Application and/or the social networking site or by sending an email to privacy.MovieBeat@cloudion.net. If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other Users have copied or saved that information.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, MovieBeat will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MovieBeat, our Users or others.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain MovieBeat services.

MovieBeat may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the MovieBeat Service. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. MovieBeat does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks MovieBeat to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. In addition, third-party advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies. The MovieBeat Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We MovieBeat takes utmost care on using commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information and implement your privacy settings.

Compromise Of Personal Information  
In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, MovieBeat will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

Your Choices About Your Information  
Will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, it will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom MovieBeat transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

**Children's Privacy**

*MovieBeat encourages parents to spend time online with their children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers, without permission, when using the Internet. No information may be submitted to MovieBeat by persons under the age of 13 without the consent of a parent or guardian, unless permitted by applicable laws.

*If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to MovieBeat he or she can contact us via email as listed below.

* Responsible measures will be taken upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13.

*Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after onlinerealgames.com deletes the information from its active database.

**Notification Procedures**

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by MovieBeat in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes in our privacy policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on the Service to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, Please Contact: contactus.moviebeat@cloudion.net
